[
    {
    "option1": "They had been going.",
    "option2": "They have going.",
    "option3": "They have been going.",
    "option4": "They have been gone.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে থাকছে",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They will be going.",
    "option2": "They will been going.",
    "option3": "They will going.",
    "option4": "They shall be going.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে থাকবে",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They were going.",
    "option2": "They had  going.",
    "option3": "They had be gone.",
    "option4": "They had been going.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে থাকছিলো",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had they been going ?",
    "option2": "Have they been going ?",
    "option3": "Have they been gone ?",
    "option4": "Are they been going ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে থাকছে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will they be go ?",
    "option2": "Shall they be going ?",
    "option3": "Will they going ?",
    "option4": "Will they be going ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে  থাকবে ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Have they been going ?",
    "option2": "Had they been going ?",
    "option3": "Had they be going ?",
    "option4": "Were they been going ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে থাকছিলো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They has gone.",
    "option2": "They had gone.",
    "option3": "They were gone.",
    "option4": "They did gone.",
    "question": "তারা গেল",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Are they gone ?",
    "option2": "Did they gone ?",
    "option3": "Has they gone ?",
    "option4": "Had they gone ?",
    "question": "তারা  কি গেল ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They could have gone.",
    "option2": "They could gone.",
    "option3": "They could have go.",
    "option4": "They could have going.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে পারতো",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Can they have gone ?",
    "option2": "Could they have go ?",
    "option3": "Could they had gone ?",
    "option4": "Could they have gone ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে পারতো ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They would had gone.",
    "option2": "They would have gone.",
    "option3": "They will have gone.",
    "option4": "They would have go.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে পারতো",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Would they  gone ?",
    "option2": "Would they have go ?",
    "option3": "Would they had gone ?",
    "option4": "Would they have gone ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে পারতো ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They should have gone.",
    "option2": "They should have went.",
    "option3": "They shall have gone.",
    "option4": "They should have going.",
    "question": "তাদের  যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Should they had gone ?",
    "option2": "Should they have gone ?",
    "option3": "Shall they have gone ?",
    "option4": "Can they have gone ?",
    "question": "তাদের কি যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They may had gone.",
    "option2": "They may have gone.",
    "option3": "They can have gone.",
    "option4": "They may have go.",
    "question": "তারা যেতে পারতো",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Shall they have gone ?",
    "option2": "May they had gone ?",
    "option3": "May they have gone ?",
    "option4": "May they have go ?",
    "question": "তারা কি যেতে পারতো ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They cannot but go.",
    "option2": "They cannot but gone.",
    "option3": "They can but go.",
    "option4": "They cannot  go.",
    "question": "তারা না গিয়ে পারে না",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "They cannot help go.",
    "option2": "They cannot help going.",
    "option3": "They can help going.",
    "option4": "They cannot help gone.",
    "question": "তারা না গিয়ে পারে না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]